zooshoo.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy | ZOOSHOO

ZooShoo.com understands and respects how your personal information is used and shared. Your privacy and security of your personal information is very important to us.

##### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES ZOOSHOO.COM GATHER AND USE?

ZooShoo.com uses the information from customers to helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at ZooShoo.com.

##### INFORMATION COLLECTION:

We collect your name, billing & shipping address, phone number, credit card information, and email for the sole purpose of processing your order and for internal marketing purposes. E-mail communication helps us make shopping with ZooShoo.com easier, quicker, and convenient for our customers. Your email address will be used strictly for sending your order and shipping confirmations, and for relevant correspondence regarding your order. We may send you occasional email notices relating to our products or promotions. If you do not wish to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by sending an email to: service@zooshoo.com.

##### IS IT SAFE TO SHOP ON ZOOSHOO.COM?

This site, ZooShoo.com, incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. Ordering from ZooShoo.com is safe and secure as we use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption from the moment you proceed to checkout, you are on a secure server. Your credit card and personal information is encrypted when transmitted to us in a secure environment. The encryption keeps your personal information, including credit card information, protected from theft. ZooShoo.com is actively monitored 24/7 to make sure that we are always open, safe, and available for your shopping experience. 

##### WHAT ARE COOKIES AND HOW DOES ZOOSHOO.COM USE THEM?

A cookie is a small piece of information that a website stores on a personal computer and which it can later retrieve. This allows us to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. We may use cookies for administrative purposes, for example, to store our customers' preference for various products or to save a password for quick access each time you visit zooshoo.com. Cookies will not contain information that will enable anyone to contact our customer via telephone, email, or any other means. If our customers are uncomfortable with the use of cookie technology, they may set their browsers to refuse cookies.

##### WHAT ABOUT THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS AND OTHER WEBSITES?

Zooshoo.com respects your privacy and does not sell, rent, or give away any customer's information to any other party. We do reserve the right, however, to do so in the future without prior notice or consent. You may, however, at any time, request for us to remove your information from our records and we will respect your privacy.

##### UPDATES TO THIS POLICY:

Our business is continually evolving, and our Privacy Notice and Terms and Conditions will change at any given time. We may send an e-mail reminder of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to. We will post any changes and updates on this site so that the information will be available on what data we collect, use, and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if any policy has been changed or updated.
